{
    "questions" : [
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "64_1_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Customer, what's the problem?\nMan : I can't see the laptop screen.\nWoman : Yes, when did you buy it?",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "64_2_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "Man : Hold the ball well and look at the front.\nWoman : Like this? What do you do next?\nMan : Walk slowly and roll the ball.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [1~3] 다음을 듣고 알맞은 그림을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "64_3_img",
            "option_1"      : "①  ",
            "option_2"      : "②  ",
            "option_3"      : "③  ",
            "option_4"      : "④  ",
            "detail"        : "Men : The number of spectators visiting cinemas has continued to decline since 2015. The reason for the decrease in the number of viewers was 'because of the variety of activities', followed by 'the number of people watching movies on mobile' and 'the viewing fee has increased'.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  ",
            "score"         : "2",
            "isImg"         : "y"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "4. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  모임 장소로 오세요",
            "option_2"      : "②  내일은 갈 수 있어요",
            "option_3"      : "③  고향에서 친구가 와서요",
            "option_4"      : "④  못 만날까 봐 걱정했어요",
            "detail"        : "Woman : I don't think I can go to the meeting tomorrow.\nMan : Why? What's going on?\nWoman : A friend came from my hometown.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  고향에서 친구가 와서요",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "5. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  아니, 머리는 괜찮아졌어",
            "option_2"      : "②  응, 내가 약을 사다 줄게",
            "option_3"      : "③  아니, 문을 안 열었더라고",
            "option_4"      : "④  응, 늦게까지 하는 약국이 있어",
            "detail"        : "Man : I'll buy some medicine and bring it. My head keeps hurting\nWoman : Is there a pharmacy that is still open at this time?\nMan : Yes, there's a pharmacy that stays up late.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  응, 늦게까지 하는 약국이 있어",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "6. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  그럼 토요일에 보자",
            "option_2"      : "②  그럼 내가 가서 물어볼게",
            "option_3"      : "③  연습실은 3층으로 가면 돼",
            "option_4"      : "④  주말에 연습이 없는 줄 알았어",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Can I use the practice room on the 3rd floor on Saturday?\nMan : I don't know because I haven't talked to the management office yet.\nWoman : Then I'll go and ask.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  그럼 내가 가서 물어볼게",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "7. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  공사를 하면 깨끗해지겠어요",
            "option_2"      : "②  공사는 내일부터 시작한대요",
            "option_3"      : "③  공사를 해서 시끄러울 거예요",
            "option_4"      : "④  공사가 빨리 끝났으면 좋겠어요",
            "detail"        : "Man : I can't concentrate on my work because of the construction noise.\nWoman : That's right. There is a lot of dust.\nMan : I hope the construction will be finished soon.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  공사가 빨리 끝났으면 좋겠어요",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [4~8]다음 대화를 잘듣고 이어질 수있는 말을 고르십시오.(각2점)",
            "question"      : "8. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  첫 방송이 정말 기대되네요",
            "option_2"      : "②  시청자 의견을 못 들었어요",
            "option_3"      : "③  장면들이 아름다웠다고 해요",
            "option_4"      : "④  음악에 더 신경을 써야겠네요",
            "detail"        : "Woman : What is the viewer's opinion on the first broadcast?\nMan : There were a lot of opinions that it was fun. But the music doesn't fit the scene.\nWoman : I should pay more attention to the music.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  음악에 더 신경을 써야겠네요",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "9. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  꽃을 가져온다",
            "option_2"      : "②  선물을 고른다",
            "option_3"      : "③  생일 카드를 쓴다",
            "option_4"      : "④  민수한테 전화한다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : I bought a present and prepared flowers, and what happened to the cake?\nMan: Minsu said he was going to buy the cake.\nWoman : Then I should be using some birthday cards.\nMan : Okay, I'll call where Minsu is from.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  생일 카드를 쓴다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "10. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  검사 예약을 한다",
            "option_2"      : "②  옷을 갈아입으러 간다",
            "option_3"      : "③  진료 시간을 확인한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  탈의실 위치를 물어본다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Well, I made an appointment at 2 o'clock today. This is Kim Soo-mi.\nMan : Yes, the reservation has been confirmed. You need to change your clothes before the examination.\nWoman : Is that so? Where should I go?\nMan : If you go to the right, there is a dressing room.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  옷을 갈아입으러 간다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "11. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  화분에 물을 준다",
            "option_2"      : "②  화분에 날짜를 붙인다",
            "option_3"      : "③  화분에 토마토를 심는다",
            "option_4"      : "④  화분을 베란다로 옮긴다",
            "detail"        : "Man : I've attached the date of planting tomatoes, so it's all over now.\nWoman : Planting tomatoes is simpler than I thought.\nMan : Isn't it? Now I'll move the pot to the veranda, so you give me some water.\nWoman : Yes, I see.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  화분에 물을 준다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [9~12]다음 대화를 잘 듣고 여자가 이어서 할행 동으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "12. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  다른 강사를 찾아본다",
            "option_2"      : "②  박 선생님에게 연락한다",
            "option_3"      : "③  특강 자료를 정리한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  연수 프로그램을 알아본다",
            "detail"        : "Man : Kim Soo-mi, has the employee training program been confirmed?\nWoman : I haven't been able to find someone to give a special lecture yet. I'm going to contact Mr. Park Min-seok today.\nMan : Then please hurry up. If it doesn't work, I have to find someone else.\nWoman : Yes, I'll find out right away.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  박 선생님에게 연락한다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "13. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  여자는 심리학과 학생이다",
            "option_2"      : "②  여자는 수강 신청을 하지 못했다",
            "option_3"      : "③  남자는 심리학 개론 수업에 만족했다",
            "option_4"      : "④  남자는 여자와 심리학 개론 수업을 들었다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Minsu, you took an introductory psychology class last year, didn't you?\nMan : yeah. It was really good Are you going to take that class, too?\nWoman : I signed up for the course, but I'm worried because it's a class in another department.\nMan : The class, the content is fun and not difficult, so it will be fine.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  남자는 심리학 개론 수업에 만족했다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "14. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  노래자랑 대회는 오후에 한다",
            "option_2"      : "②  어울림 축제는 저녁에 시작한다",
            "option_3"      : "③  올해 처음으로 야시장이 열린다",
            "option_4"      : "④  수영장은 놀이터 안에 설치됐다",
            "detail"        : "Man : Residents, tomorrow is the day of our apartment's harmony festival. A mini swimming pool for children will be installed next to the playground, and a night market will be held this year as well as last year. At 3 p.m., various events are prepared, starting with the singing contest, so please participate.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  노래자랑 대회는 오후에 한다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "15. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 열차는 현재 운행 중이다",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 열차는 인주역에 들어오지 못했다",
            "option_3"      : "③  이 열차는 지난주에도 정전 사고가 있었다",
            "option_4"      : "④  이 열차의 정전 사고는 늦은 밤에 발생했다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Around 8 a.m. today, there was a power outage on the subway line 3 train at Inju Station. The accident train stopped for 10 minutes, and the citizens suffered a lot of inconvenience on the way to work. There was a power outage on this train last week.We are currently suspending service and conducting a thorough inspection.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  이 열차는 지난주에도 정전 사고가 있었다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [13~16] 다음을 듣고 내용과 일치하는 것을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "16. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  병든 나무에는 직접 약을 처방하지 않는다",
            "option_2"      : "②  남자는 나무 치료를 시작한 지 얼마 안 됐다",
            "option_3"      : "③  남자는 나무 치료를 위해 땅의 상태를 조사한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  나무는 다른 식물에 비해 환경의 영향을 덜 받는다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : You've been treating trees for a long time. How do you treat trees?\nMan : Examine the symptoms of a sick tree, and examine the condition of the ground and the surrounding trees. Because trees are as sensitive to the surrounding environment as other plants. Depending on the cause of the disease, improve the surrounding environment or prescribe medicine directly on the tree.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  남자는 나무 치료를 위해 땅의 상태를 조사한다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "17. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  운동을 제대로 배워서 하고 싶다",
            "option_2"      : "②  인터넷의 운동 정보는 도움이 된다",
            "option_3"      : "③  건강을 위해 꾸준히 운동을 해야 한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  따라 하기 쉬운 요가 영상을 선택해야 한다",
            "detail"        : "Man : I think I should go to a yoga academy. I exercise by myself, so I don't know if the movement is right and it doesn't seem to work.\nWoman : There are a lot of online yoga videos these days, so why don't you watch them?\nMan : I don't think video alone is possible. You can't know even if my movements are wrong.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  운동을 제대로 배워서 하고 싶다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "18. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  갈등이 생기면 빨리 해결해야 한다",
            "option_2"      : "②  자신의 생각을 분명하게 말하면 좋겠다",
            "option_3"      : "③  상대방이 원하는 것을 먼저 하는 게 좋다",
            "option_4"      : "④  상대방의 입장을 이해하려면 대화가 필요하다",
            "detail"        : "Man : Sumiya, why don't you say anything? Tell me where you want to go too.\nWoman : I don't care where. Just do it where many people want.\nMan : If you want to make a decision that everyone can be satisfied with, you have to tell me exactly what you think.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  자신의 생각을 분명하게 말하면 좋겠다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "19. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "① 이 명함은 디자인이 인상적이어서 좋다",
            "option_2"      : "② 이 명함은 디자인에 더 신경을 써야 한다",
            "option_3"      : "③ 이 명함은 정보를 충분히 넣을 필요가 있다",
            "option_4"      : "④ 이 명함은 명함을 준 사람에 대해 알기 쉽다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : This is the business card I got a while ago. The design is so unique, isn't it?\nMan : I see It's also impressive to have a picture.\nWoman : But don't you think there's a lack of information to be called a business card?\nMan: I think it's good to see it one more time like this thanks to the design.",
            "correctAnswer" : "① 이 명함은 디자인이 인상적이어서 좋다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [17~20] 다음을 듣고 남자의 중심 생각을 고르십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "20. 2점",
            "option_1"      : "①  기업 행사는 분위기 연출이 가장 어렵다",
            "option_2"      : "②  기업 행사는 행사의 목적을 고려해야 한다",
            "option_3"      : "③  기업 행사는 프로그램이 다양할수록 좋다",
            "option_4"      : "④  기업 행사는 직원들이 만족할 수 있어야 한다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : What should I pay attention to when planning a corporate event?\nMan : You need to figure out what the purpose of the event is. The event to promote the new product should create an atmosphere according to the image of the product. Events for employees, such as year-end party, require various programs for friendship.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  기업 행사는 행사의 목적을 고려해야 한다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "21. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  여행객들의 성향을 조사해야 한다",
            "option_2"      : "②  고객 만족도를 높이는 것이 우선이다",
            "option_3"      : "③  이용 후기를 늘릴 수 있도록 해야 한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  후기 분석을 적극적으로 할 필요가 있다",
            "detail"        : "Man : According to the recent survey data, it is said that the reviews that travelers refer to the most when choosing a hotel.\nWoman : That's right. I think we should pay more attention to post-review management, too. Our hotel has high customer satisfaction, but there are few reviews.\nMan : So we need to actively inform our customers about writing reviews.It is the same Let's also do an event that allows us to leave a lot of reviews.\nWoman : that's good then think about what kind of event would be good.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  이용 후기를 늘릴 수 있도록 해야 한다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [21~22] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "22. 들은 내용으로 알맞은 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  이 호텔에서는 후기 작성 이벤트를 하고 있다",
            "option_2"      : "②  남자는 호텔과 관련된 자료를 조사할 예정이다",
            "option_3"      : "③  이 호텔을 이용한 고객들은 후기를 많이 남겼다",
            "option_4"      : "④  여자가 일하는 호텔은 고객 만족도가 높은 편이다",
            "detail"        : "Man : According to the recent survey data, it is said that the reviews that travelers refer to the most when choosing a hotel.\nWoman : That's right. I think we should pay more attention to post-review management, too. Our hotel has high customer satisfaction, but there are few reviews.\nMan : So we need to actively inform our customers about writing reviews.It is the same Let's also do an event that allows us to leave a lot of reviews.\nWoman : that's good then think about what kind of event would be good.",
            "correctAnswer" : "④  여자가 일하는 호텔은 고객 만족도가 높은 편이다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [23~24] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "23. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  면허증 재발급 방법을 문의하고 있다",
            "option_2"      : "②  면허증 재발급 기간을 확인하고 있다",
            "option_3"      : "③  면허 시험장의 위치를 알아보고 있다",
            "option_4"      : "④  면허증 발급을 위한 서류를 요청하고 있다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Hello. I lost my driver's license, so I want to get it issued again.What should I do?\nMan : If you come to the driver's license test center, you can get it on the same day. When you come you must bring your ID.\nWoman : Can't I apply on the Internet? The license test center is too far away.\nMan : It's also available on the Internet. When you apply, you can designate a nearby police station and get your license. But it takes about two weeks.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  면허증 재발급 방법을 문의하고 있다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "24. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  경찰서에서도 면허증을 받을 수 있다",
            "option_2"      : "②  여자는 인터넷으로 신청서를 제출했다",
            "option_3"      : "③  여자는 면허 시험장에서 가까운 곳에 있다",
            "option_4"      : "④  인터넷을 이용하면 당일에 면허증 발급이 가능하다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Hello. I lost my driver's license, so I want to get it issued again.What should I do?\nMan : If you come to the driver's license test center, you can get it on the same day. When you come you must bring your ID.\nWoman : Can't I apply on the Internet? The license test center is too far away.\nMan : It's also available on the Internet. When you apply, you can designate a nearby police station and get your license. But it takes about two weeks.",
            "correctAnswer" : "①  경찰서에서도 면허증을 받을 수 있다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "25. 남자의 중심 생각으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  소방관의 근무 환경을 개선해야 한다",
            "option_2"      : "②  사람들이 소방관에 대해 관심을 가지면 좋겠다",
            "option_3"      : "③  사람들은 소방관의 희생정신을 본받아야 한다",
            "option_4"      : "④  소방관의 안전을 보장하기 위한 대책이 필요하다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Today, I came to meet college students who became a hot topic by making bags that recycled firefighting suits. How did you come to do this?\nMan : I wanted to let you know how hard the firefighters are working in a difficult environment for the citizens. So, since last year, we have been recycling discarded firefighting suits to make bags using our major. Since the material of the bag is unique, I was able to attract people's attention naturally and even sold it. Currently, the proceeds from the sale of bags are being used to inform firefighters of their activities. I hope our small efforts will remind us of the difficulties of firefighters once more.",
            "correctAnswer" : "②  사람들이 소방관에 대해 관심을 가지면 좋겠다",
            "score"         : "2"
        },
        {   "sections"      : "※ [25~26] 다음을 듣고 물음에 답하십시오. (각 2점)",
            "question"      : "26. 들은 내용으로 맞는 것을 고르십시오.",
            "option_1"      : "①  남자는 소방관으로 일하고 있다",
            "option_2"      : "②  이 가방은 사람들에게 판매되지 않는다",
            "option_3"      : "③  이 가방은 소방복을 재활용해 만든 것이다",
            "option_4"      : "④  남자가 만든 가방은 아직 알려지지 않았다",
            "detail"        : "Woman : Today, I came to meet college students who became a hot topic by making bags that recycled firefighting suits. How did you come to do this?\nMan : I wanted to let you know how hard the firefighters are working in a difficult environment for the citizens. So, since last year, we have been recycling discarded firefighting suits to make bags using our major. Since the material of the bag is unique, I was able to attract people's attention naturally and even sold it. Currently, the proceeds from the sale of bags are being used to inform firefighters of their activities. I hope our small efforts will remind us of the difficulties of firefighters once more.",
            "correctAnswer" : "③  이 가방은 소방복을 재활용해 만든 것이다",
            "score"         : "2"
        }
        
    ]
   
}
